Finding Aid for the Ephraim Sales Collection of Tapes and Transcripts of Interviews by Roy Newquist LSC.1494
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ephraim Sales collection of tapes and transcripts of interviews by Roy Newquist
circa 1963-1967
UCLA Library Special Collections
Sales, Ephraim
LSC.1494
10 Linear Feet (20 boxes)
Roy Newquist (b.1925) was a copy supervisor for various advertising agencies in Minneapolis and Chicago (1951-63), a literary editor for Chicago's American and a critic for the New York Post (1963). He also hosted a radio program called Counterpoint, WQXR, New York. His published books include Counterpoint (1964) and Conversations (1967). The collection consists of audiotape recorded interviews and documentation related to interviews of various authors and entertainers conducted by Newquist.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
This collection contains processed audio materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ephraim Sales, 1986.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9929767403606533
Biography
Newquist was born July 25, 1925 in Ashland Wisconsin; attended Marquette University (1943-46) and University of Wisconsin (1946-49); copy supervisor for various advertising agencies in Minneapolis and Chicago, 1951-63; became literary editor for Chicago's American and a critic for the New York Post in 1963; hosted a radio program called Counterpoint, WQXR, New York; published books include Counterpoint (1964) and Conversations (1967).
Scope and Content
Collection consists of audiotape recorded interviews and documentation related to interviews of various authors and entertainers conducted by Roy Newquist.
Transcripts.; Audiotapes.; Entertainers -- Interviews.; Authors -- Interviews.; Broadcasters -- United States -- Archives.; Periodical editors -- Archives.; Newquist, Roy
- Abel, Robert H. (Writer)., 1963 September.; (10pp.) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Ace, Goodman (Writer)., 131 (Box 10)
  General note
  (No transcript available)
- Adamson, Joy (Writer)., 185 (Box 12)
  - Joy Adamson, 1964; yrlsc1494_012_185; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:59:20) (Box 12, Case 185)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
- Aghayan, Raymond (Film costume designer) -- Transcript., (7pp.) (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Albee, Edward (Writer)., 2 (Box 1)
- Albee, Edward (Writer)., 24 (Box 2)
- Albee, Edward (Writer)., 79 (Box 6)
- Albee, Edward (Writer)
  See: Who's afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Box 20).
- Aldrich, Robert (Film producer)., 193 (Box 13)
  - Robert Aldrich, Michael Caine, undated; yrlsc1494_013_193b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:48) (Box 13, Case 193)
- Amara, Lucine (Opera singer)., 34 (Box 3)
  - Lucine Amara, Pamela Tiffin, undated; yrlsc1494_003_034a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:17) (Box 3, Case 34)
  - Lucine Amara, Pamela Tiffin, undated; yrlsc1494_003_034b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:46:12) (Box 3, Case 34)
- Amara, Lucine (Opera singer)., 79 (Box 6)
  - Lucine Amara, Edward Albee, undated; yrlsc1494_006_079a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:13:24) (Box 6, Case 79)
  - Lucine Amara, Edward Albee, undated; yrlsc1494_006_079b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:53:29) (Box 6, Case 79)
- Andrews, Julie (Actress)., 70 (Box 5)
  - Julie Andrews, Mary Tyler Moore, undated; yrlsc1494_005_070a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:20) (Box 5, Case 70)
    Scope and Contents
    Content Note: End of interview with Andrews, beginning of interveiw with Moore
  - Julie Andrews, Mary Tyler Moore, undated; yrlsc1494_005_070b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:38) (Box 5, Case 70)
- Andrews, Julie (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.30., (21pp.) (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Ann-Margaret (Actress)., 106 (Box 8)
  - Ann-Margret, undated; yrlsc1494_008_106a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:54) (Box 8, Case 106)
  - Ann-Margret, undated; yrlsc1494_008_106b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:06) (Box 8, Case 106)
- Auchincloss, Louis (Writer)., 109 (Box 8)
  (UCLA has Copyright)
  - Counterpoint: Louis Auchincloss, 1964 May 29; yrlsc1494_008_109; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:11:28) (Box 8, Case 109)
- Austin, Pamela., ([Color transparencies], 9pp.) (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Bacall, Lauren (Actress)., 69 (Box 5)
  - Lauren Bacall, undated; yrlsc1494_005_069a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:53:52) (Box 5, Case 69)
  - Lauren Bacall, undated; yrlsc1494_005_069b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:38:57) (Box 5, Case 69)
- Barrett, Mary Ellen (Writer)., 68 (Box 5)
  - Ralph Ginzburg, Mary Ellin Barrett, undated; yrlsc1494_005_068a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:32) (Box 5, Case 68)
  - Ralph Ginzburg, Mary Ellin Barrett, undated; yrlsc1494_005_068b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:25) (Box 5, Case 68)
- Barrett, Mary Ellen (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.68., (19pp.) (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Barry, Naomi (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (13pp.) (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Bassing, Eileen (Writer)., 26 (Box 2)
  - Counterpoint: Eileen Bassing, 1964 May 5; yrlsc1494_002_026; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:11:14) (Box 2, Case 26)
- Beard, James (Writer)., 16 (Box 2)
  - James Beard, undated; yrlsc1494_002_016; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:20) (Box 2, Case 16)
- Beard, James (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.16., (13pp.) (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Beatty, Warren (Actor)., 41 (Box 3)
- Beatty, Warren (Actor)., 99 (Box 8)
  - Warren Beatty, 1964 March 27; yrlsc1494_008_099a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:02) (Box 8, Case 99)
  - Warren Beatty, 1964 March 27; yrlsc1494_008_099b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:57) (Box 8, Case 99)
- Beatty, Warren (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.99., (50pp.) (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Beatty, Warren (Actor)., 126 (Box 9)
- Bennett, Lerone (Writer)., 128 (Box 10)
  - Lerone Bennett, undated; yrlsc1494_010_128a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:04:13) (Box 10, Case 128)
  - Lerone Bennett, undated; yrlsc1494_010_128b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:18) (Box 10, Case 128)
- Bennett, Lerone (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.128., (15pp.) (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Bishop, Joey (Actor)., 137 (Box 10)
  - Joey Bishop, undated; yrlsc1494_010_137; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:08) (Box 10, Case 137)
- Black, Karen (Actress)., 78 (Box 6)
  - Karen Black, undated; yrlsc1494_006_078a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:26) (Box 6, Case 78)
  - Karen Black, undated; yrlsc1494_006_078b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:26) (Box 6, Case 78)
- Blatty, William (Writer)., 17 (Box 2)
- Blocker, Dan (Actor). -- Transcript., 1967 October; (50pp.) (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Borge. Victor (Actor)., 1965 March 10.; 191 (Box 13)
  - Victor Borge, 1965; yrlsc1494_013_191; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:37:47) (Box 13, Case 191)
- Borge. Victor (Actor). -- Transcript of Tape no.191., 1965 March 10; (10pp.) (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Bourke-White, Margaret (Photographer)., 9 (Box 1)
  - Margaret Bourke White, undated; yrlsc1494_001_009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:41) (Box 1, Case 9)
- Bradley, Van Allen (Literary critic) -- Transcript., (20pp.) (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Bronson, Bill (Writer) -- Transcript., (17pp.) (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Brooks, Gwendolyn (Writer)., 56 (Box 4)
  - Counterpoint II: Gwendolyn Brooks, undated; yrlsc1494_004_056a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:08) (Box 4, Case 56)
    Content Note: Interview begins on side B
  - Counterpoint II: Gwendolyn Brooks, undated; yrlsc1494_004_056b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:58) (Box 4, Case 56)
- Brown, Helen Gurley (Writer)., 129 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified, Helen Gurley Brown, undated; yrlsc1494_010_129a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:10) (Box 10, Case 129)
  - Unidentified, Helen Gurley Brown, undated; yrlsc1494_010_129b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:27:05) (Box 10, Case 129)
- Brown, Helen Gurley (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.129., (17pp.) (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Brown, Helen Gurley (Writer)., 152 (Box 11)
  - Helen Gurley Brown, 1964 September 1; yrlsc1494_011_152; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:52) (Box 11, Case 152)
- Brown, Helen Gurley (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.152., (19pp.) (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Burton, Richard (Actor)., 2 (Box 1)
- Burton, Richard (Actor)., 25 (Box 2)
  - Richard Burton, Robert St. John, undated; yrlsc1494_002_025a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:38:35); Condition Notes: Recording is hard to hear in places and speed changes toward the end (Box 2, Case 25)
  - Richard Burton, Robert St. John, undated; yrlsc1494_002_025b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:35) (Box 2, Case 25)
- Burton, Richard (Actor)., 172 (Box 12)
  - Richard Burton, undated; yrlsc1494_012_172; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:54:34) (Box 12, Case 172)
- Burton, Richard (Actor)
- Caine, Michael (Actor)., 50 (Box 4)
  - Michael Caine, undated; yrlsc1494_004_050a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:04:50) (Box 4, Case 50)
  - Michael Caine, undated; yrlsc1494_004_050b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:50) (Box 4, Case 50)
- Caine, Michael (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.50., (16pp.) (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Caine, Michael (Actor)., 130 (Box 10)
  Transcript, 10pp. missing.
  - Michael Caine, Cliff Roberston, 1970; yrlsc1494_010_130a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:46:34) (Box 10, Case 130)
  - Michael Caine, Cliff Roberston, 1970; yrlsc1494_010_130b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:46:34) (Box 10, Case 130)
- Caine, Michael (Actor)., 193 (Box 13)
  Transcript, 6pp. missing.
- Caldwell, Zoe (Writer)., 173 (Box 12)
- Calisher, Hortense (Writer)., 1963 September.; 42 (Box 3)
  - Hortense Calisher, undated; yrlsc1494_003_042; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:12) (Box 3, Case 42)
- Calisher, Hortense (Writer). -- Transcript of Tape no.42., 1963 September; (2pp.) (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Callahan, Kristina. ______ [Guthrie Theater]., 167 (Box 12)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor)., 18 (Box 2)
  - Maureen O'Sullivan II, Godfrey Cambridge, undated; yrlsc1494_002_018; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:10:30) (Box 2, Case 18)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor)., 38 (Box 3)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, undated; yrlsc1494_003_038a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:52) (Box 3, Case 38)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, undated; yrlsc1494_003_038b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:47) (Box 3, Case 38)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.38., (69pp.) (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor)., 40 (Box 3)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, Maureen O'Sullivan I, Henry Fonda Continued, undated; yrlsc1494_003_040a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:41) (Box 3, Case 40)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, Maureen O'Sullivan I, Henry Fonda Continued, undated; yrlsc1494_003_040b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:31); Condition Note: Speed slows down in first half of recording (Box 3, Case 40)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor)., 43 (Box 4)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, Stanley Kramer II, Katharine Houghton, undated; yrlsc1494_004_043a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:03); Condition Note: Speed varies throughout recording (Box 4, Case 43)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, Stanley Kramer II, Katharine Houghton, undated; yrlsc1494_004_043b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:51:43); Condition Note: Speed varies throughout recording (Box 4, Case 43)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor)., 44 (Box 4)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, undated; yrlsc1494_004_044a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:53:50) (Box 4, Case 44)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, undated; yrlsc1494_004_044b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:05:20) (Box 4, Case 44)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.44., (35pp.) (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Cambridge, Godfrey (Actor)., 120 (Box 9)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, Henry Fonda, undated; yrlsc1494_009_120a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:21:41); Condition Note: Speed increases toward end of recording (Box 9, Case 120)
  - Godfrey Cambridge, Henry Fonda, undated; yrlsc1494_009_120b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:00) (Box 9, Case 120)
- Canned Heat. Musicians -- Transcript., (21pp.) (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Cerf, Bennet (Publisher, writer). -- Transcript., 1963 July; (12pp.) (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Chad (of Chad and Jeremy) (Singer)., 89 (Box 7)
- Chad (of Chad and Jeremy) (Singer) -- Transcript of Tape no.89., (23pp.) (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Channing, Carol (Actress)., 66 (Box 5)
  - Carol Channing, Richard Quine, Catherine Spaak, Robert Kirsch, undated; yrlsc1494_005_066a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:27) (Box 5, Case 66)
  - Carol Channing, Richard Quine, Catherine Spaak, Robert Kirsch, undated; yrlsc1494_005_066b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:56); Condition Note: recording speeds up toward the end (Box 5, Case 66)
- Channing, Carol (Actress)., 108 (Box 8)
- Channing, Carol (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.108., (16pp.) (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Charell, Lisa (Actress)., 1 (Box 1)
- Charell, Lisa (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.1., (16pp.) (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Chase, Ilka (Actress, author)., 14 (Box 1)
  - Ilka Chase, undated; yrlsc1494_001_014; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:27:33) (Box 1, Case 14)
- Clark, Eleanor (Writer)., 135 (Box 10)
  - Eleanor Clark and Robert Penn Warren, undated; yrlsc1494_010_135a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:31) (Box 10, Case 135)
  - Eleanor Clark and Robert Penn Warren, undated; yrlsc1494_010_135b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:36) (Box 10, Case 135)
- Collins, Larry - La Pierre, Dennis (Writers)., 183 (Box 12)
  - Larry Collins, Dominique Lapierre, Jesse Hill Ford, undated; yrlsc1494_012_183b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:02:07) (Box 12, Case 183)
- Comer, Anjanette (Actress) -- Transcript., (6pp.) (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Condon, Richard (Writer)., 171 (Box 12)
  - Richard Condon, undated; yrlsc1494_012_171; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:45:03) (Box 12, Case 171)
- Condon, Richard (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.171., (16pp.) (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Cooley, Leland (Writer)., 17 (Box 2)
  - Leland Cooley, William Blatty, Basil Rathbone, 1963 September 1; yrlsc1494_002_017; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:51) (Box 2, Case 17)
- Cooley, Leland (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.17., (4pp.) (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Crichton, Robert (Writer)., 62 (Box 5)
- Crichton, Robert (Writer)., 123 (Box 9)
- Cronyn, Hume (Actor)., 174 (Box 12)
  - Hume Cronyn, undated; yrlsc1494_012_174a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:23) (Box 12, Case 174)
  - Hume Cronyn, undated; yrlsc1494_012_174b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:18) (Box 12, Case 174)
- Cronyn, Hume (Actor)., 190 (Box 13)
  - Hume Cronyn, undated; yrlsc1494_013_190b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:41) (Box 13, Case 190)
- Crosby, John (Writer)., 178 (Box 12)
- Cukor, George (Director)., 74 (Box 6)
  - George Cukor, Joyce Selznick, undated; yrlsc1494_006_074a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:42:08) (Box 6, Case 74)
    Content Note: discussing Katharine Hepburn
  - George Cukor, Joyce Selznick, undated; yrlsc1494_006_074b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:42:05) (Box 6, Case 74)
- Daves, Jessica (Writer)., 1 (Box 1)
- Daves, Jessica (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.1., (10pp.) (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Day, Doris (Actress)., 118 (Box 9)
- De Mille, Agnes (Choreographer). -- Transcript., 1963 December; (16pp.) (Box 16, Folder 2)
- De Sica, Vittorio (Director) -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Dennis, Sandy (Actress)., 2 (Box 1)
  Also, See: Who's afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Box 20).
- Diller, Phyllis (Actress) -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Diller, Phyllis (Actress)., 35 (Box 3)
  - Phylis Diller, Jack Palance, undated; yrlsc1494_003_035a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:01) (Box 3, Case 35)
  - Phylis Diller, Jack Palance, undated; yrlsc1494_003_035b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:13:01) (Box 3, Case 35)
- Diller, Phyllis (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.35., (27pp.) (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Doctor X (Writer)., 189 (Box 13)
  - Doctor X, undated; yrlsc1494_013_189; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:53:33); Condition note: silent portion in the first 10 minutes of the recording (Box 13, Case 189)
    Content note: Doctor X is a pseudonym for author, Alan E. Nourse, who did not want to me identified at the time of this interview
- Dolbier, Maurice (Literary critic). -- Transcript., 1964 March; (16pp.) (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Drury, Allan (Writer)., 112 (Box 8)
- Durant, Mary (Writer)., 10 (Box 1)
  - William Jovanovich, Mary Durant, 1963 September 1; yrlsc1494_001_010; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:42:07) (Box 1, Case 10)
- Durant, Mary (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.10., (8pp.) (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Durant, Will, - Durant, Ariel (Writers) -- Transcript., (1p.) (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Eastwood, Clint (Actor)., 97 (Box 7)
  - Clint Eastwood, "Chuck" and psychiatrist, undated; yrlsc1494_007_097a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:56) (Box 7, Case 97)
    Content Note: second half of side A and the entirety of Side B feature personal conversation between "Chuck" and a psychiatrist
  - Clint Eastwood, "Chuck" and psychiatrist, undated; yrlsc1494_007_097b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:44:43) (Box 7, Case 97)
- Edelman, Maurice (Politician, writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (16pp.) (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Epstein, Seymour (Writer)., 183 (Box 12)
  - Bernard Rudofsky, Seymour Epstein, undated; yrlsc1494_012_183a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:02); Condition note: recording speeds up at the end (Box 12, Case 183)
- Evans, Dame Edith (Actress)., 180 (Box 12)
  - Dame Edith Evans, 1965; yrlsc1494_012_180; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:34) (Box 12, Case 180)
- Fast, Howard (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 February; (13pp.) (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Faulk, John Henry (Radio commentator)., 153 (Box 11)
  - John Henry Faulk, undated; yrlsc1494_011_153; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:40:22) (Box 11, Case 153)
- Fielding, Gabriel (Writer)., 22 (Box 2)
- Fielding, Gabriel (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.22., (20pp.) (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Flanner, Janet [Genet] (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 November; (24pp.) (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Fleming, Ian (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; 127; (9pp.) (Box 10)
  - Counterpoint: Ian Fleming, undated; yrlsc1494_010_127; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:11:16) (Box 10, Case 127)
- Fleming, Ian (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (9pp.) (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Fonda, Henry (Actor)., 1963 June 6.; 3 (Box 1)
  - Henry Fonda, undated; yrlsc1494_001_003a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:18); Condition Notes: recording is slightly hard to hear due to changes in speed (Box 1, Case 3)
    Content Note: features same recording as uclayrlsc1494_001_004a
- Fonda, Henry (Actor)., 1963 June 6.; 4 (Box 1)
  - Henry Fonda, 1963 June 6; yrlsc1494_001_004a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:27:47); Condition Notes: recording is slightly hard to hear due to changes in speed (Box 1, Case 4)
  - Henry Fonda, undated; yrlsc1494_001_004b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:12) (Box 1, Case 4)
- Fonda, Henry (Actor). -- Transcript of Tape no.4., 1963 June 6; (73pp.) (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Fonda, Henry (Actor)., 40 (Box 3)
- Fonda, Henry (Actor)., 81 (Box 6)
  - Henry Fonda, undated; yrlsc1494_006_081a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:14:33); Condition Note: Speed changes throughout recording (Box 6, Case 81)
  - Henry Fonda, undated; yrlsc1494_006_081b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:14); Condition Note: Speed changes throughout recording (Box 6, Case 81)
- Fonda, Henry (Actor)., 120 (Box 9)
- Forbes-Robinson, Diana (Writer)., 157 (Box 11)
  - Diana Forbes-Roberston, 1964 May 1; yrlsc1494_011_157; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:04) (Box 11, Case 157)
- Ford, Jesse Hill (Writer)., 183 (Box 12)
- Foreman, Carl (Director)., 53 (Box 4)
  - Carl Foreman, undated; yrlsc1494_004_053; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:38:19) (Box 4, Case 53)
- Foreman, Eve. ______., 49 (Box 4)
- Fowles, John (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (13pp.) (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Franchi, Sergio (Actor)., 82 (Box 6)
  - Sergio Franchi, Anna Magnani, undated; yrlsc1494_006_082a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:37:20) (Box 6, Case 82)
  - Sergio Franchi, Anna Magnani, undated; yrlsc1494_006_082b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:37:10) (Box 6, Case 82)
- Franchi, Sergio (Actor)., 123 (Box 9)
  - Sergio Franchi, Robert Chrichton, undated; yrlsc1494_009_123a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:24); Condition Note: speed increases toward end of recording (Box 9, Case 123)
  - Sergio Franchi, Robert Crichton, undated; yrlsc1494_009_123b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:24) (Box 9, Case 123)
- Frank, Gerold (Writer)., 23 (Box 2)
  - Gerold Frank, undated; yrlsc1494_002_023a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:00:25) (Box 2, Case 23)
    Content Note: Introduction to interview with Paul McClelland on Side A
  - Gerold Frank, undated; yrlsc1494_002_023b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:40) (Box 2, Case 23)
- Frankau, Pamela (Writer)., 192 (Box 13)
  - Pamela Frankau, undated; yrlsc1494_013_192; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:37) (Box 13, Case 192)
- Garner, James (Actor)., 32 (Box 3)
  - James Garner, Don Stroud, undated; yrlsc1494_003_032a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:39) (Box 3, Case 32)
  - James Garner, Don Stroud, undated; yrlsc1494_003_032b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:39:54) (Box 3, Case 32)
- Garner, James (Actor)., 86 (Box 7)
  - James Garner, undated; yrlsc1494_007_086a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:19) (Box 7, Case 86)
  - James Garner, undated; yrlsc1494_007_086b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:18:34) (Box 7, Case 86)
- Gary, Romain (Writer)., 132 (Box 10)
  - Romain Gary, Lennon Sisters, undated; yrlsc1494_010_132a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:11) (Box 10, Case 132)